

Varun Khachane

B.Tech – Computer Science Engineering (AIML) github.com/vk2122 S.R.M. Institute of Science & Technology

+91-9313615925 varunkhachane31@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/varunkhachane

Summary

Experienced Member with a demonstrated history of working in the non-profit organization management industry. Skilled in English, Management, Communication, Leadership, and Project Management. Strong media and communication pursuing Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Computer Engineering (Specialization AI/ML) from SRM University.

Education

Degree/Certificate	Institute/Board	CGPA/Percentage	Year
B.Tech. CSE Major	SRM Institute of Science & Technology, Chennai	9.21 (Current)	2020-Present
Senior Secondary	SRS Gnyan Dham School/CBSE Board	79.2%	2020
Secondary	SRS Gnyan Dham School/CBSE Board	84.4%	2018

Work Experience

• Research Internship

Indian Institute of Science & Technology

January 2023 – February 2023 IIT-Guwahati

Remote, Chennai

• Flutter Internship

Flutter Developer, Obroo India

October 2022 – December 2022

Projects

• OnBoarding App for Banks

- A one stop app solution for banking firms to onboard new customers directly using a mobile app
- Tech Stack: Flutter, Dart, MongoDB, NodeJs, AWS, Machine Learning

• Mall Customer Segmentation Analysis

- Malls or shopping complexes are often indulged in the race to increase their customers and hence make huge profits.
- Tech Stack: Machine Learning (Regression Algorithms), Python, Flask

• Student Management System

- Python-Django-MySQL project, where Python is used to design the frontend using Tkinter libraries of python, Django is used as a connector for transmitting data from the front to the database in the backend, the backend was designed using MySQL software
- Tech Stack: Python, Django, MySQL

Technical Skills

- **Programming:** C, C++, Python, Data Structure and Algorithms, Competitive Programming, Problem Solving
- Tools/Frameworks: Flask, Dart, Flutter, MongoDB, NodeJs, Git/GitHub
- **Miscellaneous Skills**: Arduino Programming, Hands-on experience in Hardware training(Raspberry Pi, Nvidia Jetson) Teamwork, Communication, Leadership, Project Management

Position of Responsibility

•	Corporate Head, PLACFV'S (Student Placement Team)	February 2023 - present
•	Corporate Associate CodeChef SRM Chapter	Ianuary 2021 - May 2022

Achievement

•	1 st Position - Data Stellar Hackathon,	April 2023
	Barclays	
•	Runner's Up - Hacktrix Hackathon	May 2022
	IEEE SRM	·
•	Certificate of Participation, AlgoStrike2.0 (Coding Contest)	March 2022
	INDIAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, DHARWAD	